<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<lang module="lang_onconfig">
<ADMIN_MODE_USERS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies which users (in addition to user informix and DBSA group users) can access the database server in administration mode.]]></ADMIN_MODE_USERS_DESC>
<ADMIN_USER_MODE_WITH_DBSA_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether user <i>informix</i> and the DBSA group users can connect to the database server while it is in administration mode.]]></ADMIN_USER_MODE_WITH_DBSA_DESC>
<ADTERR_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) ADTERR specifies how the database server behaves when it encounters an error while it writes an audit record.]]></ADTERR_DESC>
<ADTMODE_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) Controls the level of auditing.]]></ADTMODE_DESC>
<ADTPATH_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) Specifies the directory in which the database server saves audit files.]]></ADTPATH_DESC>
<ADTSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) Specifies the maximum size of an audit file.]]></ADTSIZE_DESC>
<AFCRASH_DESC><![CDATA[When the 0x10 bit is on for AFCRASH, all the messages that the Java Virtual Machine generates are logged into the JVM_vpid file, where vpid is the process ID of the Java virtual processor. This file is stored in the directory where the JVPLOG file is stored.]]></AFCRASH_DESC>
<AFFAIL_DESC><![CDATA[]]></AFFAIL_DESC>
<AFF_NPROCS_DESC><![CDATA[On multiprocessor computers that support processor affinity, AFF_NPROCS specifies the number of CPUs to which the database server can bind CPU virtual processors.]]></AFF_NPROCS_DESC>
<AFF_SPROC_DESC><![CDATA[On multiprocessor computers that support processor affinity, AFF_SPROC specifies the CPU, starting with 0, on which the database server starts binding CPU virtual processors to CPUs.]]></AFF_SPROC_DESC>
<ALARMPROGRAM_DESC><![CDATA[Displays event alarms]]></ALARMPROGRAM_DESC>
<ALLOW_NEWLINE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies that the database server allows the newline character (
) in a quoted string either for all sessions or for a specific session.]]></ALLOW_NEWLINE_DESC>
<ALRM_ALL_EVENTS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether ALARMPROGRAM runs for all events that are logged in the MSGPATH or only for noteworthy events.]]></ALRM_ALL_EVENTS_DESC>
<ASF_SOCTCP_BACKLOG_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of connections in the queue when using Sockets (SOCTCP).]]></ASF_SOCTCP_BACKLOG_DESC>
<AUTO_AIOVPS_DESC><![CDATA[Enables the database server to automatically increase the number of AIO VPs and page cleaner threads when the database server detects that the I/O workload has outpaced the performance of the existing AIO VPs.]]></AUTO_AIOVPS_DESC>
<AUTO_CKPTS_DESC><![CDATA[Allows the server to trigger checkpoints more frequently to avoid transaction blocking.]]></AUTO_CKPTS_DESC>
<AUTO_LRU_TUNING_DESC><![CDATA[Enables automatic LRU tuning]]></AUTO_LRU_TUNING_DESC>
<AUTO_READAHEAD_DESC><![CDATA[Changes the automatic read-ahead mode or disables automatic read ahead.  Automatic read-ahead operations help improve query performance by issuing asynchronous page requests when the database server detects that the query is encountering I/O.  0 = Disable automatic read-ahead requests.  1 = Enable automatic read-ahead requests in the standard mode.  2 = Enable automatic read-ahead requests in the aggressive mode.]]></AUTO_READAHEAD_DESC>
<AUTO_REPREPARE_DESC><![CDATA[Controls whether a Dynamic Server feature is in effect that automatically re-optimizes SPL routines and re-prepares prepared objects after the schema of a table referenced by the SPL routine or by the prepared object has been changed.]]></AUTO_REPREPARE_DESC>
<AUTO_STAT_MODE_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables automatically updating statistics for the database server.]]></AUTO_STAT_MODE_DESC>
<BACKUP_FILTER_DESC><![CDATA[Secifies the pathname of a filter program, and any options.]]></BACKUP_FILTER_DESC>
<BAR_ACT_LOG_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the location of the ON-Bar activity log file.]]></BAR_ACT_LOG_DESC>
<BAR_BSALIB_PATH_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the pathname and filename of the XBSA shared library for the storage manager.]]></BAR_BSALIB_PATH_DESC>
<BAR_CKPTSEC_TIMEOUT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the amount of time, in seconds, that an RS secondary server should wait for a checkpoint to arrive from the primary server while performing an external backup. If a backup fails because the checkpoint from the primary has timed out, you can use the BAR_CKPTSEC_TIMEOUT configuration parameter to increase the amount of time that an RS secondary server should wait for a checkpoint to arrive from the primary server.]]></BAR_CKPTSEC_TIMEOUT_DESC> 
<BAR_DEBUG_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the level of debugging messages in the ON-Bar activity log.]]></BAR_DEBUG_DESC>
<BAR_DEBUG_LOG_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the location of the ON-Bar debug log.]]></BAR_DEBUG_LOG_DESC>
<BAR_HISTORY_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether the sysutils database maintains a backup history.]]></BAR_HISTORY_DESC>
<BAR_IXBAR_PATH_DESC><![CDATA[Overrides the name and path of the ON-Bar boot file.  By default, the ON-Bar boot file is created in $INFORMIXDIR/etc and has the name 'ixbar.<SERVER_NUM>'.]]></BAR_IXBAR_PATH_DESC>
<BAR_MAX_BACKUP_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of parallel backup processes that are allowed for each ON-Bar command.]]></BAR_MAX_BACKUP_DESC>
<BAR_NB_XPORT_COUNT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of shared-memory data buffers for each backup or restore process.]]></BAR_NB_XPORT_COUNT_DESC>
<BAR_PERFORMANCE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the level of performance statistics to print to the ON-Bar activity log.]]></BAR_PERFORMANCE_DESC>
<BAR_PROGRESS_FREQ_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies in minutes how frequently the backup or restore progress messages display in the activity log.]]></BAR_PROGRESS_FREQ_DESC>
<BAR_RETRY_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies how many times ON-Bar should retry a data backup, logical-log backup, or restore operation if the first attempt fails.]]></BAR_RETRY_DESC>
<BAR_SIZE_FACTOR_DESC><![CDATA[Augments the estimate for the size of a backup object, prior to the backup. The value of the BAR_SIZE_FACTOR parameter is computed as a percentage of the original backup object size, and then added to the estimate, before the estimate is communicated to the storage manager.]]></BAR_SIZE_FACTOR_DESC>
<BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size of each transfer buffer that the database server passes to ON-Bar and the storage manager.  The maximum buffer size is 64 kilobytes, so BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE * pagesize <= 64 kilobytes.]]></BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE_DESC>
<BATCHEDREAD_INDEX_DESC><![CDATA[Enables the optimizer to automatically fetch a set of keys from an index buffer. This reduces the number of times a buffer is read, thus improving performance.]]></BATCHEDREAD_INDEX_DESC>
<BATCHEDREAD_TABLE_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables light scans on compressed tables, tables with rows that are larger than a page, and tables with VARCHAR, LVARCHAR, and NVARCHAR data.]]></BATCHEDREAD_TABLE_DESC>
<BLOCKTIMEOUT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of seconds that a thread or database server will hang.]]></BLOCKTIMEOUT_DESC>
<BTSCANNER_DESC><![CDATA[Sets the B-tree scanner, which automatically determines which index items are to be deleted.]]></BTSCANNER_DESC>
<BUFFERPOOL_DESC><![CDATA[Consists of two lines in the onconfig.std file: the first line specifies the default values that are used to create a dbspace with a page size that does not already have a corresponding buffer pool created at start up; the second line specifies the database server's default values for a buffer pool.]]></BUFFERPOOL_DESC>
<BUFFERS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of shared-memory buffers that the database server user threads have available for disk I/O on behalf of client applications.]]></BUFFERS_DESC>
<CDR_APPLY_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the minimum and maximum number of data sync threads.]]></CDR_APPLY_DESC>
<CDR_DELAY_PURGE_DTC_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies how long to retain the delete tables to support the delete wins conflict resolution rule.]]></CDR_DELAY_PURGE_DTC_DESC>
<CDR_DBSPACE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the dbspace where the syscdr database is created.]]></CDR_DBSPACE_DESC>
<CDR_DSLOCKWAIT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of seconds the Datasync component waits for the database locks to be released.]]></CDR_DSLOCKWAIT_DESC>
<CDR_ENV_DESC><![CDATA[Sets the Enterprise Replication environment variables CDR_LOGDELTA, CDR_PERFLOG, CDR_ROUTER, or CDR_RMSCALEFACT.]]></CDR_ENV_DESC>
<CDR_EVALTHREADS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of group evaluator threads to create when Enterprise Replication starts, and enables parallelism.]]></CDR_EVALTHREADS_DESC>
<CDR_LOG_LAG_ACTION_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies how Enterprise Replication responds to a potential log wrap situation. Combine multiple values with +. logstage = Enable compressed logical log staging; dlog = Enable the dynamic addition of logical logs; ignore = Ignore the potential for log wrapping; ddrblock = Block client applications update activity; shutdown = Shut down Enterprise Replication on the affected server.]]></CDR_LOG_LAG_ACTION_DESC>
<CDR_LOG_STAGING_MAXSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum amount of space that Enterprise Replication uses to stage compressed log files.]]></CDR_LOG_STAGING_MAXSIZE_DESC>
<CDR_MAX_DYNAMIC_LOGS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of dynamic log file requests that Enterprise Replication can make in one server session.]]></CDR_MAX_DYNAMIC_LOGS_DESC>
<CDR_NIFCOMPRESS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the level of compression the database server uses before sending data from the source database server to the target database server.]]></CDR_NIFCOMPRESS_DESC>
<CDR_QDATA_SBSPACE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the list of up to 32 names of sbspaces that Enterprise Replication uses to store spooled transaction row data.]]></CDR_QDATA_SBSPACE_DESC>
<CDR_QHDR_DBSPACE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the location of the dbspace that Enterprise Replication uses to store the transaction record headers spooled from the send and receive queues.]]></CDR_QHDR_DBSPACE_DESC>
<CDR_QUEUEMEM_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum amount of memory that is used for the send and receive queues.]]></CDR_QUEUEMEM_DESC>
<CDR_SERIAL_DESC><![CDATA[Enables control over generating values for serial and SERIAL8 columns in tables defined for replication.]]></CDR_SERIAL_DESC>
<CDR_SUPPRESS_ATSRISWARN_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the Datasync error and warning code numbers to be suppressed in ATS and RIS files.]]></CDR_SUPPRESS_ATSRISWARN_DESC>
<CHECKALLDOMAINSFORUSER_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables checking all domains for all user names in a networked Windows environment.]]></CHECKALLDOMAINSFORUSER_DESC>
<CKPTINTVL_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the frequency, in seconds, at which the database server checks to determine whether a checkpoint is needed.]]></CKPTINTVL_DESC>
<CLEANERS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of page-cleaner threads available during the database server operation.]]></CLEANERS_DESC>
<CONSOLE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the pathname and the filename for console messages.]]></CONSOLE_DESC>
<CONVERSION_GUARD_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether the Informix server stops or continues an upgrade to a new version of the server if an error occurs during the upgrade process. 0 = Disabled. The server is not stopped. 1 = Enable a restore point and stop the upgrade if an error related to capturing restore point data occurs. 2 = Enable a restore point and continue the upgrade even if an error occurs.]]></CONVERSION_GUARD_DESC>
<DATASKIP_DESC><![CDATA[Used to avoid points of media failure.]]></DATASKIP_DESC>
<DB_LIBRARY_PATH_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a comma-separated list of valid directory prefix locations from which the database server can load external modules, such as DataBlade&reg; Modules.]]></DB_LIBRARY_PATH_DESC>
<DBCREATE_PERMISSION_DESC><![CDATA[Restricts the permission to create databases to the specified user.]]></DBCREATE_PERMISSION_DESC>
<DBSERVERALIASES_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a list of alternative dbservername, and lets you assign multiple aliases to a database server, ensuring that each entry in the sqlhosts file or registry is a unique name.]]></DBSERVERALIASES_DESC>
<DBSERVERNAME_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a unique name associated with this specific occurrence of the database server.]]></DBSERVERNAME_DESC>
<DBSPACETEMP_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a list of dbspaces that the database server uses to globally manage the storage of temporary tables.]]></DBSPACETEMP_DESC>
<DD_HASHMAX_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of tables in each hash bucket in the data-dictionary cache.]]></DD_HASHMAX_DESC>
<DD_HASHSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of tables in each hash bucket in the data-dictionary cache.]]></DD_HASHSIZE_DESC>
<DEADLOCK_TIMEOUT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of seconds that a database server thread can wait to acquire a lock.  Use this parameter only for distributed queries that involve a remote database server.]]></DEADLOCK_TIMEOUT_DESC>
<DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the default lock mode for database; it can be set to PAGE or ROW.]]></DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE_DESC>
<DEFAULTESCCHAR_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the default escape character.]]></DEFAULTESCCHAR_DESC>
<DELAY_APPLY_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies how long RS secondary servers should wait before applying logs.]]></DELAY_APPLY_DESC>
<DIRECT_IO_DESC><![CDATA[Controls the use of direct I/O for cooked files used for dbspace chunks.]]></DIRECT_IO_DESC>
<DIRECTIVES_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables the use of SQL directives.]]></DIRECTIVES_DESC>
<DISABLE_B162428_XA_FIX_DESC><![CDATA[When set to 1, ensures that applications written for versions of Dynamic server 9.40 and earlier work properly.]]></DISABLE_B162428_XA_FIX_DESC>
<DISTR_QUERY_FLAGS_DESC><![CDATA[]]></DISTR_QUERY_FLAGS_DESC>
<DRAUTO_DESC><![CDATA[Determines how a secondary database server reacts to an HDR failure. This parameter should have the same value on both HDR servers.]]></DRAUTO_DESC>
<DRDA_COMMBUFFSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size of the DRDA communications buffer.]]></DRDA_COMMBUFFSIZE_DESC>
<DRIDXAUTO_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether the primary High-Availability Data Replication (HDR) server automatically starts index replication if the secondary HDR server detects a corrupted index.]]></DRIDXAUTO_DESC>
<DRINTERVAL_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum interval in seconds between flushing of the high-availability data-replication buffer. To update synchronously, set the parameter to -1.]]></DRINTERVAL_DESC>
<DRLOSTFOUND_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the pathname to the file, dr.lostfound.timestamp.]]></DRLOSTFOUND_DESC>
<DRTIMEOUT_DESC><![CDATA[For high-availability data-replication pairs, specifies the length of time, in seconds, that a database server in a high-availability data-replication pair waits for a transfer acknowledgment from the other database server in the pair.]]></DRTIMEOUT_DESC>
<DS_HASHSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of hash buckets in the data-distribution cache that the database server uses to store and access the column statistics that the UPDATE STATISTICS statement generates in the MEDIUM or HIGH mode.]]></DS_HASHSIZE_DESC>
<DS_MAX_QUERIES_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of parallel database queries (PDQ) queries that can run concurrently.]]></DS_MAX_QUERIES_DESC>
<DS_MAX_SCANS_DESC><![CDATA[Limits the number of Parallel Database Query (PDQ)  scan threads that the database server can execute concurrently.]]></DS_MAX_SCANS_DESC>
<DS_NONPDQ_QUERY_MEM_DESC><![CDATA[Increases the amount of memory that is a available for a query that is not a Parallel Database Query (PDQ).]]></DS_NONPDQ_QUERY_MEM_DESC>
<DS_POOLSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of entries in each hash bucket in the data-distribution cache that the database server uses to store and access column statistics that the UPDATE STATISTICS statement generates in the MEDIUM or HIGH mode.]]></DS_POOLSIZE_DESC>
<DS_TOTAL_MEMORY_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the amount of memory available for PDQ queries. It should be smaller than the computer physical memory, minus fixed overhead such as operating-system size and buffer-pool size.]]></DS_TOTAL_MEMORY_DESC>
<DUMPCNT_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) Specifies the number of assertion failures for which one database server thread dumps shared memory or generates a core file by calling gcore. An assertion is a test of some condition or expression with the expectation that the outcome is true.]]></DUMPCNT_DESC>
<DUMPCORE_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) Controls whether assertion failures cause a virtual processor to dump a core image. The core file is left in the directory from which the database server was last invoked. 0 = Do not dump core image; 1 = Dump core image.]]></DUMPCORE_DESC>
<DUMPDIR_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a directory in which the database server dumps shared memory, gcore files, or messages from a failed assertion. Because shared memory can be large, set DUMPDIR to a file system with a significant amount of space. The directory to which DUMPDIR is set must exist for the server to start.]]></DUMPDIR_DESC>
<DUMPGCORE_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) Used with operating systems that support gcore. When set, the database server calls gcore whenever a virtual processor encounters an assertion failure. The gcore utility directs the virtual processor to dump a core image to the core.pid.cnt file in the directory that DUMPDIR specifies and continue processing. 0 = Do not dump gcore; 1 = Dump gcore.]]></DUMPGCORE_DESC>
<DUMPSHMEM_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) Indicates that shared memory should be dumped on an assertion failure. All the shared memory that the database server uses is dumped; it is probably quite large. The shared-memory dump is placed in the shmem.pid.cnt file in the directory that DUMPDIR specifies. 0 = Do not dump shared memory; 1 = Dump shared memory.]]></DUMPSHMEM_DESC>
<DYNAMIC_LOGS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the level of dynamic log allocation for the database server.  0 = No dynamic log allocation; 1 = Alerts when a log is required and pauses to allow manual allocattion of a logical log; 2 = Dynamic log allocation is on, with alerts when each log is dynamically added.]]></DYNAMIC_LOGS_DESC>
<EILSEQ_COMPAT_MODE_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables checking whether character data that is inserted by a client application contains code point sequences that are not recognized by the current locale. 0 = Validate incoming character sequences with the current locale. 1 = Do not validate incoming character sequences.]]></EILSEQ_COMPAT_MODE_DESC>
<ENABLE_SNAPSHOT_COPY_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables the ability to clone a server by using the ifxclone utility.]]></ENABLE_SNAPSHOT_COPY_DESC>
<ENCRYPT_CDR_DESC><![CDATA[Sets the level of encryption for Enterprise Replication.  0 = do not encrypt; 1 = encrypt when possible; 2 = always encrypt.]]></ENCRYPT_CDR_DESC>
<ENCRYPT_CIPHERS_DESC><![CDATA[Defines all ciphers and modes that can be used by the current database session. ENCRYPT_CIPHERS is used for Enterprise Replication and High-Availability Data Replication only.]]></ENCRYPT_CIPHERS_DESC>
<ENCRYPT_HDR_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables HDR encryption; 0 = Disable HDR encryption, 1 = Enable HDR encryption.]]></ENCRYPT_HDR_DESC>
<ENCRYPT_MAC_DESC><![CDATA[Controls the level of message authentication code (MAC) generation and is used for Enterprise Replication and High-Availability Data Replication only. 'Off' = does not use MAC generation, 'low' = uses XOR folding on all messages, 'medium' = uses SHA1 MAC generation for all messages greater than 20 bytes long and XOR folding on smaller messages, 'high' = uses SHA1 MAC generation on all messages. For example: ENCRYPT_MAC medium,high]]></ENCRYPT_MAC_DESC>
<ENCRYPT_MACFILE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a list of the full path names of message authentication code (MAC) key files and is used for Enterprise Replication and High-Availability Data Replication only.]]></ENCRYPT_MACFILE_DESC>
<ENCRYPT_SMX_DESC><![CDATA[Sets the level of encryption for high-availability secondary server configurations. 0 =  No encryption; 1 = Encryption where possible - encryption is used for SMX transactions only when the target database server also supports encryption; 2 = Always encrypt - only connections to encrypted database servers are allowed.]]></ENCRYPT_SMX_DESC>
<ENCRYPT_SWITCH_DESC><![CDATA[Defines the frequency at which ciphers or secret keys are renegotiated. The default time that this renegotiation occurs is once an hour. ENCRYPT_SWITCH is used for Enterprise Replication and High-Availability Data Replication only.]]></ENCRYPT_SWITCH_DESC>
<EXPLAIN_STAT_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables the inclusion of a Query Statistics section in the explain output file.]]></EXPLAIN_STAT_DESC>
<EXT_DIRECTIVES_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables the use of external SQL directives. Enables external directives by using the EXT_DIRECTIVES configuration parameter in combination with the client-side IFX_EXTDIRECTIVES environment variable.<br><br>0 = Off. The directive cannot be enabled even if IFX_EXTDIRECTIVES is on.<br>1 = On. The directive can be enabled for a session if IFX_EXTDIRECTIVES is on.<br>2 = On. The directive can be used even if IFX_EXTDIRECTIVES is not set.]]></EXT_DIRECTIVES_DESC>
<EXTSHMADD_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size of extension virtual segments that you add. Range of values is 1024 through 524,288 kilobytes.]]></EXTSHMADD_DESC>
<FAILOVER_CALLBACK_DESC><![CDATA[The database server executes the script specified by FAILOVER_CALLBACK when a database server transitions from a secondary server to a primary or standard server. Set FAILOVER_CALLBACK to the full pathname of the script.]]></FAILOVER_CALLBACK_DESC>
<FAILOVER_TX_TIMEOUT_DESC><![CDATA[In high-availability cluster environments, indicates the maximum number of seconds after failover that the server waits before rolling back transactions. This can enable transactions to be completed.]]></FAILOVER_TX_TIMEOUT_DESC>
<FASTPOLL_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables fast polling of the network. FASTPOLL is platform specific. 0 = Disables fast polling; 1 = Enables fast polling.]]></FASTPOLL_DESC>
<FILLFACTOR_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the degree of index-page fullness from 1-100. A low value provides room for growth in the index. A high value compacts the index. If an index is full (100 percent), any new inserts result in splitting nodes. ]]></FILLFACTOR_DESC>
<FULL_DISK_INIT_DESC><![CDATA[Enables a safeguard that prevents the accidental disk initialization of an existing database server instance. Specifies whether the disk initialization command can run when the first page of the first chunk (page zero) exists at the root path location. 0 = The oninit -i command runs only if there is no page zero at the root path location. 1 = The oninit -i command runs under all circumstances, but also resets the FULL_DISK_INIT configuration parameter to 0 after the disk initialization.]]></FULL_DISK_INIT_DESC>
<GSKIT_VERSION_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the major version of the IBM&reg; Global Security Kit (GSKit) that the database server uses for encryption and SSL communication.]]></GSKIT_VERSION_DESC>
<HA_ALIAS_DESC><![CDATA[When a secondary server connects to a primary server, specifies the name of a network alias to use if a failover occurs.]]></HA_ALIAS_DESC>
<HETERO_COMMIT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether or not the database server is prepared to participate with IBM Informix Gateway products in heterogeneous commit transactions. 1 = Enable heterogeneous commit; 0 = Disable heterogeneous commit.]]></HETERO_COMMIT_DESC>
<IFX_EXTEND_ROLE_DESC><![CDATA[Enables the database server administrator (DBSA), by default user informix, to implement security measures that establish which users can register DataBlade&reg; modules or user-defined routines (UDRs); 1 or On (default) = Enables the EXTEND role so that administrators can grant privileges to a user to create or drop a UDR that has the EXTERNAL clause; 0 or Off = Disables the EXTEND role so that any user can register an external routine.]]></IFX_EXTEND_ROLE_DESC>
<IFX_FOLDVIEW_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables view folding; 0 or Off (default) = Disables view folding, 1 or On = Enables view folding.]]></IFX_FOLDVIEW_DESC>
<INDEX_SELFJOIN_DESC><![CDATA[]]></INDEX_SELFJOIN_DESC>
<ISM_DATA_POOL_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the volume pool for backing up storage spaces.]]></ISM_DATA_POOL_DESC>
<ISM_LOG_POOL_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the volume pool for backing up logical logs.]]></ISM_LOG_POOL_DESC>
<JDKVERSION_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the version number of the Java Development Kit (JDK) or Java Runtime Environment (JRE) release ]]></JDKVERSION_DESC>
<JVPARGS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies Java VM options.]]></JVPARGS_DESC>
<JVPDEBUG_DESC><![CDATA[When set to 1, writes tracing messages to the JVPLOG file.]]></JVPDEBUG_DESC>
<JVPHOME_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the directory where the classes of the IBM Informix JDBC Driver are installed.]]></JVPHOME_DESC>
<JVPLOGFILE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the absolute pathname for your Java VP log files.]]></JVPLOGFILE_DESC>
<JVPPROPFILE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the absolute pathname for the Java VP properties file.]]></JVPPROPFILE_DESC>
<JVPJAVAVM_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the libraries to use for the Java Virtual Machine (JVM).]]></JVPJAVAVM_DESC>
<JVPJAVAHOME_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the directory where the Java Runtime Environment (JRE) for the database server is installed.]]></JVPJAVAHOME_DESC>
<JVMTHREAD_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the thread package (green or native) to use for the JVM.]]></JVMTHREAD_DESC>
<JVPJAVALIB_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the path from JVPJAVAHOME to the location of the Java VM libraries.]]></JVPJAVALIB_DESC>
<JVPCLASSPATH_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the initial Java class path setting.]]></JVPCLASSPATH_DESC>
<LIMITNUMSESSIONS_DESC><![CDATA[Defines the maximum number of sessions to connect to the Informix database server, and whether the database server should print warning messages to the online.log file when the number of sessions approaches the maximum number.]]></LIMITNUMSESSIONS_DESC>
<LISTEN_TIMEOUT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of seconds the server waits for a connection.]]></LISTEN_TIMEOUT_DESC>
<LOCKS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the initial size of the lock table. The lock table holds an entry for each lock that a session uses.]]></LOCKS_DESC>
<LOG_INDEX_BUILDS_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables index page logging.]]></LOG_INDEX_BUILDS_DESC>
<LOG_STAGING_DIR_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the directory where the log files from the primary server are stored when delayed application of log files on RS secondary servers is enabled.]]></LOG_STAGING_DIR_DESC>
<LOGBUFF_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size in kilobytes for the three logical-log buffers in shared memory. Triple buffering permits user threads to write to the active buffer while one of the other buffers is being flushed to disk. If you are using RTO_SERVER_RESTART, set LOGBUFF to 256 kilobytes.]]></LOGBUFF_DESC>
<LOGFILES_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of logical-log files that the database server creates during disk initialization. To change the number of logical-log files, add or drop logical-log files.]]></LOGFILES_DESC>
<LOGSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies, in kilobytes, the size that is used when logical-log files are created. It does not change the size of existing logical-log files. The total logical-log size is LOGSIZE * LOGFILES.]]></LOGSIZE_DESC>
<LOW_MEMORY_MGR_DESC><![CDATA[Enables automatic low memory management, which you can use to change the default behavior of the server when it reaches its memory limit. 1 = Enables automatic low memory management when the database server starts. 0 = Disables automatic low memory management.]]></LOW_MEMORY_MGR_DESC>
<LOW_MEMORY_RESERVE_DESC><![CDATA[Reserves a specific amount of memory, in kilobytes, for use when critical activities (such as rollback activities) are needed and the server has limited free memory.]]></LOW_MEMORY_RESERVE_DESC>
<LRUS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of LRU (least-recently-used) queues in the shared-memory buffer pool.]]></LRUS_DESC>
<LRU_MAX_DIRTY_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the percentage of modified pages in the LRU queues at which the queue is cleaned.]]></LRU_MAX_DIRTY_DESC>
<LRU_MIN_DIRTY_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the percentage of modified pages in the LRU queues at which page cleaning is no longer mandatory.]]></LRU_MIN_DIRTY_DESC>
<LTAPEBLK_DESC><![CDATA[When using ontape, specifies the block size of the device to which the logical logs are backed up. LTAPEBLK also specifies the block size for the device to which data is loaded or unloaded when using the -l option of onload or onunload. For onload or onunload, specify a different block size at the command line.]]></LTAPEBLK_DESC>
<LTAPEDEV_DESC><![CDATA[When using ontape, specifies the device or directory file system to which the logical logs are backed up. It also specifies the device to which data is loaded or unloaded when using the -l option of onload or onunload.]]></LTAPEDEV_DESC>
<LTAPESIZE_DESC><![CDATA[For ontape, specifies the maximum tape size of the device to which the logical logs are backed up. LTAPESIZE also specifies the maximum tape size of the device to which data is loaded or unloaded when using the -l option of onload or onunload. When using onload or onunload, specify a different tape size on the command line. To use the full capacity of a tape, set LTAPESIZE to 0.]]></LTAPESIZE_DESC>
<LTXEHWM_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the long-transaction, exclusive-access, high-watermark. A transaction is long if it is not committed or rolled back when it reaches the long-transaction high-watermark. When the logical-log space reaches the value of the LTXEHWM threshold, the long transaction currently being rolled back is given exclusive access to the logical log.]]></LTXEHWM_DESC>
<LTXHWM_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the long-transaction high-watermark. The long-transaction high-watermark is the percentage of available log space that, when filled, triggers the database server to check for a long transaction.]]></LTXHWM_DESC>
<MAX_FILL_DATA_PAGES_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables ability to add more rows to be inserted per page in tables that have variable-length rows; 0 = Disabled, 1 = Enabled.]]></MAX_FILL_DATA_PAGES_DESC>
<MAX_INCOMPLETE_CONNECTIONS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of incomplete connections in a session. After this number is reached, an error message is written in the online message log stating that the server might be under a Denial of Service attack. Default is 1024]]></MAX_INCOMPLETE_CONNECTIONS_DESC>
<MAX_PDQPRIORITY_DESC><![CDATA[Limits the PDQ resources that the database server can allocate to any one DSS query.]]></MAX_PDQPRIORITY_DESC>
<MIRROR_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables mirroring for the database server. It is recommended that you mirror the root dbspaces and the critical data as part of initialization; 0 = disable mirroring,1 = enable mirroring.]]></MIRROR_DESC>
<MIRROROFFSET_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the offset into the disk partition or into the device required to reach the chunk that serves as the mirror for the initial chunk of the root dbspace.]]></MIRROROFFSET_DESC>
<MIRRORPATH_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the full pathname of the mirrored chunk for the initial chunk of the root dbspace. MIRRORPATH should be a link to the chunk pathname of the actual mirrored chunk. Select a short pathname for the mirrored chunk.]]></MIRRORPATH_DESC>
<MSG_DATE_DESC><![CDATA[When enabled, adds a date to the beginning of each message in the online log.]]></MSG_DATE_DESC>
<MSGPATH_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the full pathname of the message-log file. The database server writes status messages and diagnostic messages to this file during operation.]]></MSGPATH_DESC>
<MULTIPROCESSOR_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether the database server performs locking in a manner that is suitable for a single-processor computer or a multiprocessor computer; 0 = No multiprocessor, 1 = Multiprocessor available]]></MULTIPROCESSOR_DESC>
<MQCHLLIB_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the path to the directory containing the IBM&reg; WebSphere&reg; MQ client channel definition table.]]></MQCHLLIB_DESC>
<MQCHLTAB_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the name of the IBM&reg; WebSphere&reg; MQ client channel definition table.]]></MQCHLTAB_DESC>
<MQSERVER_DESC><![CDATA[Defines a channel, specifies the location of the IBM&reg; WebSphere&reg; MQ server, and specifies the communication method to be used.]]></MQSERVER_DESC>
<NET_IO_TIMEOUT_ALARM_DESC><![CDATA[Controls whether to be notified if network write operations have been blocked for 30 minutes or more.]]></NET_IO_TIMEOUT_ALARM_DESC>
<NETTYPE_DESC><![CDATA[Describes a network connection.]]></NETTYPE_DESC>
<NOAGE_DESC><![CDATA[Some operating systems lower the priority of processes as the processes run over a long period of time. NOAGE, when set to 1, disables priority aging of CPU virtual processors by the operating system. When NOAGE is set to the default of 0, the operating system might lower the priority of CPU virtual processors, as well as other processes, as they accumulate processing time. If your operating system supports priority aging, it is recommended that you set NOAGE to 1.]]></NOAGE_DESC>
<NO_DESC_FOUND_DESC><![CDATA[No specifies which users (in addition to user informix and DBSA group users) can access the database server in administration mode.]]></NO_DESC_FOUND_DESC>
<NS_CACHE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the expiration time for obtaining name service information for host, service, user, and group connections from an internal database server cache.]]></NS_CACHE_DESC>
<NUMAIOVPS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of virtual processors of the AIO class to run. Unless kernel asynchronous I/O is implemented, the AIO virtual processors perform all the database server disk I/O, other than I/O to the log files.<BR>Virtual Processor administration can be performed within OpenAdmin on the <A href='index.php?act=vps&do=global'> Virtual Processors page </A>]]></NUMAIOVPS_DESC>
<NUMCPUVPS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of virtual processors of the CPU class to run. CPU virtual processors run all threads that start as the result of a connection by a client application, as well as internal threads.<BR>Virtual Processor administration can be performed within OpenAdmin on the <A href='index.php?act=vps&do=global'> Virtual Processors page </A>]]></NUMCPUVPS_DESC>
<NUMFDSERVERS_DESC><![CDATA[On UNIX, specifies the maximum number of poll threads to handle network connections migrating between Informix virtual processors (VPs).]]></NUMFDSERVERS_DESC>
<OFF_RECVRY_THREADS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of recovery threads used in logical recovery when the database server is offline (during a cold restore). This number of threads is also used to roll forward logical-log records in fast recovery.]]></OFF_RECVRY_THREADS_DESC>
<ON_RECVRY_THREADS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of recovery threads that the database server uses for logical recovery when the database server is online (during a warm restore).]]></ON_RECVRY_THREADS_DESC>
<ONDBSPACEDOWN_DESC><![CDATA[Defines the action that the database server takes when any disabling event occurs on a primary chunk within a noncritical dbspace.<br><br>0 = The database server marks the dbspace as offline and continues.<br>1 = The database server aborts.<br>2 = The database server writes the status of the chunk to the logs and waits for user input.]]></ONDBSPACEDOWN_DESC>
<ONLIDX_MAXMEM_DESC><![CDATA[Limits the amount of memory allocated to a single preimage pool and a single updator log pool. The preimage and updator log pools, pimage_partnum and ulog_partnum, are shared memory pools that are created when a CREATE INDEX ONLINE statement is executed. The pools are freed when the execution of the statement is completed.]]></ONLIDX_MAXMEM_DESC>
<OPCACHEMAX_DESC><![CDATA[(UNIX) Specifies the size of the memory cache for the Optical Subsystem. Use this parameter only if you use the Optical Subsystem.]]></OPCACHEMAX_DESC>
<OPT_GOAL_DESC><![CDATA[Enables one of two optimization goals for queries: Optimize for FIRST ROWS, Optimize for ALL ROWS; 0 = FIRST_ROWS. -1 = ALL_ROWS, the default.]]></OPT_GOAL_DESC>
<OPTCOMPIND_DESC><![CDATA[Helps the optimizer choose an appropriate query plan for the  application.<br><br>0 = When appropriate indexes exist for each ordered pair of tables, the optimizer chooses index scans, over table scans. This value ensures compatibility with previous versions of the database server.<br>1 = The optimizer uses costs to determine an execution path if the isolation level is not Repeatable Read. This setting is recommended for optimal performance.<br>2 = The optimizer uses cost to determine an execution path for any isolation level. Index scans are not given preference over table scans. This value is the default if the variable is not set.]]></OPTCOMPIND_DESC>
<OPTICAL_LIB_PATH_DESC><![CDATA[If you use an optical storage manager, set OPTICAL_LIB_PATH to the location of the optical storage manager library.]]></OPTICAL_LIB_PATH_DESC>
<PAM_STACKSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Customizes the stack size for PAM modules.]]></PAM_STACKSIZE_DESC>
<PC_HASHSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of hash buckets in the UDR caches that the database server uses.]]></PC_HASHSIZE_DESC>
<PC_POOLSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of UDRs stored in the UDR cache.]]></PC_POOLSIZE_DESC>
<PHYSBUFF_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size, in kilobytes, of the two physical-log buffers in shared memory. The value of the PHYSBUFF parameter determines how frequently the database server needs to flush the physical-log buffer to the physical-log file.]]></PHYSBUFF_DESC>
<PHYSDBS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the name of the dbspace that contains the physical log. To reduce disk contention, you can move the physical log to a dbspace other than the root dbspace. <BR>Physical log administration within OpenAdmin can be peformed at <A href='index.php?act=rlogs&do=admin'> Recovery Logs -> Admin </A>]]></PHYSDBS_DESC>
<PHYSFILE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size of the physical log. PHYSFILE can be changed dynamically with the onparams utility. <BR>Physical log administration within OpenAdmin can be peformed at <A href='index.php?act=rlogs&do=admin'> Recovery Logs -> Admin </A>]]></PHYSFILE_DESC>
<PLCY_HASHSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of hash buckets in the security policy information cache.]]></PLCY_HASHSIZE_DESC>
<PLCY_POOLSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of entries in each hash bucket of the user LBAC credential information cache.]]></PLCY_POOLSIZE_DESC>
<PLOG_OVERFLOW_PATH_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the location of the file used during fast recovery if the physical log file overflows. The file name is plog_extend.servernum and is by default located in /tmp. Use the full pathname to specify a different location.]]></PLOG_OVERFLOW_PATH_DESC>
<PN_STAGEBLOB_THRESHOLD_DESC><![CDATA[Reserves space for BYTE and TEXT data in round-robin fragments.]]></PN_STAGEBLOB_THRESHOLD_DESC>
<PRELOAD_DLL_FILE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the path name for a shared library file or a dynamic link library file (DLL) that is loaded when the database server is initialized. If multiple files are loaded, each path name is specified with a separate entry.]]></PRELOAD_DLL_FILE_DESC>
<QSTATS_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables onstat -g qst to print queue statistics; 0 = Disable queue statistics, 1 = Enable queue statistics]]></QSTATS_DESC>
<RA_PAGES_DESC><![CDATA[If you disable the AUTO_READAHEAD configuration parameter, use the RA_PAGES configuration parameter to define the number of disk pages to attempt to read ahead. When the AUTO_READAHEAD configuration parameter is enabled and read ahead occurs automatically, the server ignores information specified in the RA_PAGES configuration parameter.]]></RA_PAGES_DESC>
<RA_THRESHOLD_DESC><![CDATA[Used with RA_PAGES when the database server reads during sequential scans of data records. RA_THRESHOLD specifies the read-ahead threshold; that is, the number of unprocessed data pages in memory that signals the database server to perform the next read-ahead. If the value of RA_THRESHOLD is greater than the value of RA_PAGES, RA_THRESHOLD has a value of RA_PAGES/2.]]></RA_THRESHOLD_DESC>
<RAS_LLOG_SPEED_DESC><![CDATA[]]></RAS_LLOG_SPEED_DESC>
<RAS_PLOG_SPEED_DESC><![CDATA[]]></RAS_PLOG_SPEED_DESC>
<REDIRECTED_WRITES_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of SMX pipes between the primary and secondary server.]]></REDIRECTED_WRITES_DESC>
<RESIDENT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether resident and virtual segments of shared memory remain resident in operating-system physical memory.<BR><BR>0 = off<BR>1 = lock the resident segment only<BR>n = lock the resident segment and the next n-1 virtual segments<BR>-1 = lock all resident and virtual segments]]></RESIDENT_DESC>
<REMOTE_SERVER_CFG_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the name of a file that lists the remote hosts that are trusted by the computer on which the database server resides.]]></REMOTE_SERVER_CFG_DESC>
<REMOTE_USERS_CFG_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the name of a file that lists names of trusted users that exist on remote hosts.]]></REMOTE_USERS_CFG_DESC>
<RESTARTABLE_RESTORE_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables the database server to restart a failed physical or cold logical restore at the point at which the failure occurred. To perform a restartable restore with ON-Bar, use the onbar -RESTART command. Increase the size of your physical log if you plan to use restartable restore. Values: On or Off ]]></RESTARTABLE_RESTORE_DESC>
<RESTORE_FILTER_DESC><![CDATA[Specify the pathname of a filter program, and any options, such as encryption.]]></RESTORE_FILTER_DESC>
<RESTORE_POINT_DIR_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the path name of the directory where the restore point files are stored during a failed upgrade to a new version of the database server.]]></RESTORE_POINT_DIR_DESC>
<ROOTNAME_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a name for the root dbspace for this database server configuration. The name must be unique among all dbspaces that the database server manages. ]]></ROOTNAME_DESC>
<ROOTOFFSET_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the offset, in kilobytes, into an allocation of disk space (file, disk partition, or device) at which the initial chunk of the root dbspace begins.]]></ROOTOFFSET_DESC>
<ROOTPATH_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the full pathname, including the device or filename, of the initial chunk of the root dbspace. ROOTPATH is stored in the reserved pages as a chunk name. On UNIX, you must set the permissions of the file that ROOTPATH specifies to 660, and the owner and group must both be informix. On Windows, a member of the Informix-Admin group must own the file that ROOTPATH specifies. ]]></ROOTPATH_DESC>
<ROOTSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size of the initial chunk of the root dbspace, in kilobytes. To change ROOTSIZE after you initialize the database server, completely unload and reload your data.]]></ROOTSIZE_DESC>
<RSS_FLOW_CONTROL_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the boundaries within which flow control is enabled in a high-availability cluster that contains at least one RS secondary server. Flow control provides a way to limit log activity on the primary server so that RS secondary servers in the cluster do not fall too far behind on processing transactions.]]></RSS_FLOW_CONTROL_DESC>
<RTO_SERVER_RESTART_DESC><![CDATA[Enables you to use recovery time objective (RTO) standards to set the amount of time, in seconds, that Dynamic Server has to recover from a problem after you restart Dynamic Server and bring the server into online or quiescent mode.]]></RTO_SERVER_RESTART_DESC>
<S6_USE_REMOTE_SERVER_CFG_DESC><![CDATA[Used with the REMOTE_SERVER_CFG configuration parameter, this parameter specifies which file is used to authenticate secure server connections in a untrusted network environment. 1 = The servers listed in the file specified by the REMOTE_SERVER_CFG configuration parameter are trusted connections. 2 = The $INFORMIXDIR/etc/host.equiv file is used to authenticate servers connecting through a secure port as defined by setting s=6 in the sqlhost information.]]></S6_USE_REMOTE_SERVER_CFG_DESC>
<SB_CHECK_FOR_TEMP_DESC><![CDATA[Prevents copying temporary smart large objects into permanent tables. 0 = Permit, 1 = Prevent.]]></SB_CHECK_FOR_TEMP_DESC>
<SBSPACENAME_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the name of the default sbspace. If your database tables include smart-large-object columns that do not explicitly specify a storage space, that data is stored in the sbspace that SBSPACENAME specifies.]]></SBSPACENAME_DESC>
<SBSPACETEMP_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the name of the default temporary sbspace for storing temporary smart large objects without metadata or user-data logging.]]></SBSPACETEMP_DESC>
<SDS_ENABLE_DESC><![CDATA[Enables SD secondary server functionality. You must set SDS_ENABLE to 1 (enable) on both the primary server and the SD secondary server to enable SD secondary server functionality.<br><br>0 = disable SD secondary server functionality.<br>1 = enable SD secondary server functionality.]]></SDS_ENABLE_DESC>
<SDS_PAGING_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the location of two files that act as buffer paging files. If SDS_PAGING is not set, the SD secondary server may fail to start.]]></SDS_PAGING_DESC>
<SDS_LOGCHECK_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the amount of time in seconds that the SD secondary server waits to detect whether the primary server is generating log activity. If there is no log activity generated by the primary server in the specified amount of time, failover processing is allowed to start. Use the SDS_LOGCHECK configuration parameter to determine whether the primary server is generating log activity and to allow or prevent failover of the primary server.]]></SDS_LOGCHECK_DESC>
<SDS_TEMPDBS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies information that the SD secondary server uses to dynamically create temporary dbspaces. ]]></SDS_TEMPDBS_DESC>
<SDS_TIMEOUT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the amount of time in seconds that the primary server will wait for a log position acknowledgement to be sent from the SD secondary server.]]></SDS_TIMEOUT_DESC>
<SECURITY_LOCALCONNECTION_DESC><![CDATA[Verifies security on local connections by ensuring that the ID of the local user who is running a program is the same ID of the user who is trying to access the database.<br><br>0 = no security checking occurs.<br>1 = Dynamic Server verifies if the ID of the user running the program matches the ID of the user who is trying to connect to the database.<br>2 = same as 1, plus Dynamic Server retrieves the peer port number from the network API and verifies that the connection is coming from the client program. Specify 2 if your system has SOCTCP or IPCSTR network protocols.]]></SECURITY_LOCALCONNECTION_DESC>
<SERVERNUM_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a relative location in shared memory from 0 to 255. The value must be unique for each database server on the local computer, but not on the network. Because the value 0 is the default in the onconfig.std file, choose a value other than 0 to avoid inadvertent duplication of SERVERNUM.]]></SERVERNUM_DESC>
<SEQ_CACHE_SIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of sequence objects that can have preallocated values in the sequence cache. If this configuration parameter is not set, then by default no more than 10 different sequence objects can be defined with the CACHE option.]]></SEQ_CACHE_SIZE_DESC>
<SHMADD_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size of a segment that is dynamically added to the virtual portion of shared memory.]]></SHMADD_DESC>
<SHMBASE_DESC><![CDATA[Do not change the value of SHMBASE. It specifies the base address where shared memory is attached to the memory space of a virtual processor. The addresses of the shared-memory segments start at the SHMBASE value and grow until the upper-bound limit, which is platform specific.]]></SHMBASE_DESC>
<SHMNOACCESS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a virtual memory address range to avoid using to attach shared memory.]]></SHMNOACCESS_DESC>
<SHMTOTAL_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the limit for the demand for memory that the database server can place on a system.]]></SHMTOTAL_DESC>
<SHMVIRT_ALLOCSEG_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies a threshold at which Dynamic Server should allocate a new memory segment and the alarm level activated if the server cannot allocate the new memory segment, thus ensuring that the server never runs out of memory. Once the alarm level is activated, it will repeat every thirty minutes if a new memory segment cannot be allocated.<br><br>Alarm level values from 1 to 5 where:<br>1 = Not noteworthy<br>2 = Information<br>3 = Attention<br>4 = Emergency<br>5 = Fatal]]></SHMVIRT_ALLOCSEG_DESC>
<SHMVIRTSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the initial size of a virtual shared-memory segment.]]></SHMVIRTSIZE_DESC>
<SINGLE_CPU_VP_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether or not the database server is running with only one CPU virtual processor. 0 = Running with more than 1 CPU VPs; Any non-zero number = Running with only 1 CPU VP.]]></SINGLE_CPU_VP_DESC>
<SMX_COMPRESS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the level of compression that the database server uses before sending data from the source database server to the target database server.]]></SMX_COMPRESS_DESC>
<SORT_MERGE_SIZE_DESC><![CDATA[]]></SORT_MERGE_SIZE_DESC>
<SP_AUTOEXPAND_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables the automatic creation or extension of chunks in a storage space.]]></SP_AUTOEXPAND_DESC>
<SP_THRESHOLD_DESC><![CDATA[Defines the minimum amount of space in the storage pool required for the database server to automatically expand a space. A value of 50 or below, indicates a percentage. A value of 1000 or higher, indicates kilobytes.]]></SP_THRESHOLD_DESC>
<SP_WAITTIME_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of seconds that a thread waits for a dbspace, temporary dbspace, sbspace, temporary sbspace, or blobspace to expand before returning an out-of-space error.]]></SP_WAITTIME_DESC>
<SQL_LOGICAL_CHAR_DESC><![CDATA[Enables or disables expanding the size specifications in declarations of built-in character data types.]]></SQL_LOGICAL_CHAR_DESC>
<SQLTRACE_DESC><![CDATA[Controls the startup environment of the SQL Trace facility.]]></SQLTRACE_DESC>
<SSL_KEYSTORE_LABEL_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the label of the server digital certificate used in the keystore database that stores Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) keys and digital certificates.]]></SSL_KEYSTORE_LABEL_DESC>
<STACKSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the stack size for the database server user threads.]]></STACKSIZE_DESC>
<STAGEBLOB_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the blobspace name for the area where the Optical Subsystem stages TEXT and BYTE data that is destined for storage on optical disk.]]></STAGEBLOB_DESC>
<STATCHANGE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the minimum percentage of change required in a table or fragment for the distribution statistics to qualify for an update when the automatic mode for UPDATE STATISTICS operations is enabled.]]></STATCHANGE_DESC>
<STMT_CACHE_DESC><![CDATA[Determines whether the database server uses the SQL statement cache.<br>0 = SQL statement cache not used.<br>1 = SQL statement cache enabled, but user sessions do not use the cache, unless they set the environment variable STMT_CACHE to 1 or execute the SQL statement SET STATEMENT CACHE ON for their session.<br>2 = SQL statement cache turned on. All statements are cached.]]></STMT_CACHE_DESC>
<STMT_CACHE_HITS_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of hits (references) to a statement before it is fully inserted in the SQL statement cache. The following table describes the possible values.<br><br>0 = Fully inserts all qualified statements in the SQL statement cache<br>n>0 = Statements are given key-only entries until number of statement hits is reached and all fully qualified statements are inserted into the cache.<br>n>1 = Prevents ad hoc queries from entering the cache.]]></STMT_CACHE_HITS_DESC>
<STMT_CACHE_NOLIMIT_DESC><![CDATA[Controls whether to insert qualified statements into the SQL statement cache. The following table describes the possible values. 0 = Prevents statements from being inserted in the cache to avoid allocating a large amount of memory for the cache; 1 = Always insert statements in the SQL statement cache regardless of the cache size.]]></STMT_CACHE_NOLIMIT_DESC>
<STMT_CACHE_NUMPOOL_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of memory pools for the SQL statement cache. To obtain information about these memory pools, use onstat -g ssc pool.]]></STMT_CACHE_NUMPOOL_DESC>
<STMT_CACHE_SIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size of the SQL statement caches in kilobytes. The new cache size takes effect the next time a statement is added to a cache.]]></STMT_CACHE_SIZE_DESC>
<STOP_APPLY_DESC><![CDATA[Stops an RS secondary server from applying log files received from the primary server.]]></STOP_APPLY_DESC>
<STORAGE_FULL_ALARM_DESC><![CDATA[Configures the frequency and severity of messages and alarms when storage spaces become full.]]></STORAGE_FULL_ALARM_DESC>
<SYSALARMPROGRAM_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the full pathname of the evidence.sh script. The database server executes evidence.sh when a database server failure occurs. Technical Support uses the output from the evidence.sh script to diagnose the cause of a database server failure. On Windows&reg;, you must enable command extensions for evidence.bat to successfully complete. ]]></SYSALARMPROGRAM_DESC>
<SYSSBSPACENAME_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the name of the sbspace in which the database server stores statistics that the UPDATE STATISTICS statement collects for certain user-defined data types.]]></SYSSBSPACENAME_DESC>
<TAPEBLK_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the block size of the device to which ontape writes during a storage-space backup. TAPEBLK also specifies the default block size of the device to which data is loaded or unloaded when you use the onload or onunload utilities.]]></TAPEBLK_DESC>
<TAPEDEV_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the device or directory file system to which ontape backs up storage spaces. TAPEDEV also specifies the default device to which data is loaded or unloaded when you use the onload or onunload utilities.]]></TAPEDEV_DESC>
<TAPESIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the size of the device to which ontape backs up storage spaces. Also specifies the size of the default device to which data is loaded or unloaded when you use onload or onunload. If you want to use the full physical capacity of a tape, set TAPESIZE to 0.]]></TAPESIZE_DESC>
<TBLSPACE_STATS_DESC><![CDATA[Turns on and off the collection of tblspace statistics. 0 = Off, 1 = On.]]></TBLSPACE_STATS_DESC>
<TBLTBLFIRST_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the first extent size of tblspace tblspace in the root dbspace.]]></TBLTBLFIRST_DESC>
<TBLTBLNEXT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the next extent size of tblspace tblspace in the root dbspace.]]></TBLTBLNEXT_DESC>
<TEMPTAB_NOLOG_DESC><![CDATA[Disables logging on temporary tables.<BR><BR>0 = Enable logical logging on temporary table operations<BR>1 = Disable logical logging on temporary table operations]]></TEMPTAB_NOLOG_DESC>
<TXTIMEOUT_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the amount of time that a participant in a two-phase commit waits before it initiates participant recovery. This parameter is used only for distributed queries that involve a remote database server.]]></TXTIMEOUT_DESC>
<UNSECURE_ONSTAT_DESC><![CDATA[Enables all users to view running SQL statements when set to '1'.]]></UNSECURE_ONSTAT_DESC>
<UPDATABLE_SECONDARY_DESC><![CDATA[Sets the number of connections to establish between the primary and secondary servers. Setting this configuration parameter enables client applications to perform update, insert, and delete operations on a high-availability secondary server.]]></UPDATABLE_SECONDARY_DESC>
<USERMAPPING_DESC><![CDATA[Indicates whether the database server accepts connections from mapped users and, if mapped users are accepted, whether they can be granted administrator privileges. BASIC = Mapped users can have basic privileges. ADMIN = Mapped users can have administrator privileges. OFF = User mapping is turned off.]]></USERMAPPING_DESC>
<USE_BATCHEDREAD_DESC><![CDATA[]]></USE_BATCHEDREAD_DESC>
<USE_KOBATCHEDREAD_DESC><![CDATA[]]></USE_KOBATCHEDREAD_DESC>
<USELASTCOMMITTED_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the isolation level for which the LAST COMMITTED feature of the COMMITTED READ isolation level is implicitly in effect.]]></USELASTCOMMITTED_DESC>
<USEOSTIME_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies whether the database server is to use subsecond precision when it obtains the current time from the operating system for SQL statements. 0 = Off, 1 = On.]]></USEOSTIME_DESC>
<USRC_HASHSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the number of hash buckets in the user LBAC credential information cache.]]></USRC_HASHSIZE_DESC>
<USRC_POOLSIZE_DESC><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of entries in each hash bucket of the user LBAC credential information cache.]]></USRC_POOLSIZE_DESC>
<USTLOW_SAMPLE_DESC><![CDATA[Enables sampling during the gathering of statistics for UPDATE STATISTICS LOW operations. For an index with more than 100K leaf pages, the collection of statistics from sampling can increase the speed of UPDATE STATISTICS LOW operations.]]></USTLOW_SAMPLE_DESC> 
<VP_MEMORY_CACHE_KB_DESC><![CDATA[Enables the database server to access the private memory blocks of your CPU VP.]]></VP_MEMORY_CACHE_KB_DESC>
<VPCLASS_DESC><![CDATA[Allows you to designate a class of virtual processors (VPs), create a user-defined VP, and specify the required parameters.]]></VPCLASS_DESC>
<WSTATS_DESC><![CDATA[Enables the onstat -g wst command to print wait statistics for threads within the system.]]></WSTATS_DESC>
<NO_DESC_FOUND><![CDATA[No Description Found]]></NO_DESC_FOUND>
<ON_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that this onconfig parameter be turned on (set to 1).]]></ON_RECOMMEND>
<OFF_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that this onconfig parameter be turned off (set to 0).]]></OFF_RECOMMEND>
<ZERO_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that this onconfig parameter be set to zero.]]></ZERO_RECOMMEND>
<NONTEMP_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that this onconfig parameter not be null and should not point to the server machine's temp directory.]]></NONTEMP_RECOMMEND>
<AFF_NPROCS_SPROC_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that difference between AFF_SPROC and AFF_NPROC be greater than the number of physical processors.  The number of physical processors on the machine is {0}.]]></AFF_NPROCS_SPROC_RECOMMEND>
<ALARMPROGRAM_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that ALARAMPROGRAM be set to "$INFORMIXDIR/etc/alarmprogram.sh" (UNIX/Linux) or "$INFORMIXDIR/etc/alarmprogram.bat" (Windows).]]></ALARMPROGRAM_RECOMMEND>
<ALARMPROGRAM_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[It appears that ALARMPROGRAM is currently not set to a valid location.]]></ALARMPROGRAM_RECOMMEND_NO>
<BAR_DEBUG_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended to keep BAR_DEBUG at 0, unless Tech Support has advised you otherwise in order to debug a specific issue.]]></BAR_DEBUG_RECOMMEND>
<BAR_NB_XPORT_COUNT_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that BAR_NB_XPORT_COUNT be set to a value between 5 and 99]]></BAR_NB_XPORT_COUNT_RECOMMEND>
<BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE_RECOMMEND_15><![CDATA[The page size of this server is 4K.  Therefore, it is recommended that BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE be set to 15.]]></BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE_RECOMMEND_15>
<BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE_RECOMMEND_31><![CDATA[The page size of this server is 2K.  Therefore, it is recommended that BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE be set to 31.]]></BAR_XFER_BUF_SIZE_RECOMMEND_31>
<BTSCANNER_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[BTSCANNER should not be null.  It should include a setting for alice scanning which is non-zero]]></BTSCANNER_RECOMMEND>
<CCFLAGS_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended to keep CCFLAGS at 0, unless Tech Support has advised you otherwise in order to debug a specific issue.]]></CCFLAGS_RECOMMEND>
<CKPTINTVL_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that CKPTINTVL be set to 30 seconds or above.]]></CKPTINTVL_RECOMMEND>
<CLEANERS_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that CLEANERS be set to the minimum of the number of VPs and the number of chunks.  On the current server, the recommended number of cleaners is: ]]></CLEANERS_RECOMMEND>
<DATASKIP_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that DATASKIP be turned be set to 'OFF'.]]></DATASKIP_RECOMMEND>
<DB_LIBRARY_PATH_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that all components in DB_LIBRARY_PATH are located in $INFOMRIXDIR.]]></DB_LIBRARY_PATH_RECOMMEND>
<DB_LIBRARY_PATH_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[This server has DB_LIBRARY_PATH components that are not located in $INFORMIXDIR.  If this is intended, for security reasons please verify that these external directories are owned by the user informix and have write permissions only for the user informix.]]></DB_LIBRARY_PATH_RECOMMEND_NO>
<DBSPACETEMP_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[DBSPACETEMP should not be null and each space listed should be an existing temporary dbspace.]]></DBSPACETEMP_RECOMMEND>
<DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE_RECOMMEND_ROW><![CDATA[Lock waits exist on the server.  It is recommended that you set DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE to 'row'.]]></DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE_RECOMMEND_ROW>
<DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[The general recommendation is to set DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE to 'row'.  If it is currently set to 'page' and lock waits exist on the server, it would be recommendeded that you change DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE to 'row'.  However, DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE is either already set to 'row' OR there are currently no lock waits on the server.]]></DEF_TABLE_LOCKMODE_RECOMMEND>
<DS_NONPDQ_QUERY_MEM_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that DS_NONPDQ_QUERY_MEM be greater than or equal to 512 kilobytes.  Also see DS_TOTAL_MEMORY, as DS_NONPDQ_QUERY_MEMORY cannot exceed 25 percent of the value of DS_TOTAL_MEMORY.]]></DS_NONPDQ_QUERY_MEM_RECOMMEND>
<DS_TOTAL_MEMORY_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[DS_TOTAL_MEMORY should be at least 2048 KB and must be greater than or equal to 4 times the size of DS_NONPDQ_QUERY_MEM.]]></DS_TOTAL_MEMORY_RECOMMEND>
<EXTSHMADD_RECOMMEND_OK><![CDATA[Based on the size of this server's extension virtual segments, the current value of EXTSHMADD follows the recommendation of the OpenAdmin Tool.]]></EXTSHMADD_RECOMMEND_OK>
<EXTSHMADD_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[Based on the size of this server's extension virtual segments, it is recommended that you increase EXTSHMADD to be greater than or equal to ]]></EXTSHMADD_RECOMMEND_NO>
<FILLFACTOR_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that FILLFACTOR be between 40 and 98 percent.]]></FILLFACTOR_RECOMMEND>
<LISTEN_TIMEOUT_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that LISTEN_TIMEOUT be greater than 2 seconds, but less than 180 seconds.]]></LISTEN_TIMEOUT_RECOMMEND>
<LOCKS_RECOMMEND_OK><![CDATA[The total number of locks for your database server has never exceeded the size specified in LOCKS, therefore the current value of LOCKS meets the recommendation of the OpenAdmin Tool.]]></LOCKS_RECOMMEND_OK>
<LOCKS_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[Your database server's lock table has exceeded the size specified in LOCKS.  Try increasing LOCKS by 10%.]]></LOCKS_RECOMMEND_NO>
<LOGBUFF_RECOMMEND_OK><![CDATA[Based on your database server's logical log writes, the current value of LOGBUFF meets the recommendation of the OpenAdmin Tool.]]></LOGBUFF_RECOMMEND_OK>
<LOGBUFF_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[Based on your database server's logical log writes, the current value of LOGBUFF is low.  Try increasing LOGBUFF by 10 percent.]]></LOGBUFF_RECOMMEND_NO>
<LTAPEBLK_RECOMMEND_LOW><![CDATA[The current setting of LTAPEBLK is low.  Take a look at your tape drive specifications, as most tape drives support larger block sizes than your current configuration.  Increasing LTAPEBLK could improve the performance of backups and restores.]]></LTAPEBLK_RECOMMEND_LOW>
<LTAPEBLK_RECOMMEND_HIGH><![CDATA[The current setting of LTAPEBLK is rather high.  Take a look at your tape drive specifications to make sure it can support such a large value.]]></LTAPEBLK_RECOMMEND_HIGH>
<LTXHWM_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[LTXHWM must be less than LTXEHWM.  It is recommended that LTXHWM be between 25 and 80 percent.]]></LTXHWM_RECOMMEND>
<LTXEHWM_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[LTXHWM must be less than LTXEHWM.  It is recommended that LTXEHWM be between 25 and 90 percent.]]></LTXEHWM_RECOMMEND>
<MULTIPROCESSOR_RECOMMEND_ON><![CDATA[Based on your system configuration, it is recommended that MULTIPROCESSOR be turned ON.]]></MULTIPROCESSOR_RECOMMEND_ON>
<MULTIPROCESSOR_RECOMMEND_OFF><![CDATA[Based on your system configuration, it is recommended that MULTIPROCESSOR be turned OFF.]]></MULTIPROCESSOR_RECOMMEND_OFF>
<NUMCPUVPS_RECOMMEND_OK><![CDATA[Based on your database server's performance, the current value of NUMCPUVPS follows the recommendation of the OpenAdmin Tool.]]></NUMCPUVPS_RECOMMEND_OK>
<NUMCPUVPS_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[Based on your database server's performance, it is recommended that you increase the NUMCPUVPS.]]></NUMCPUVPS_RECOMMEND_NO>
<NUMCPUVPS_RECOMMEND_ATMAX><![CDATA[Based on your database server's performance, it would be recommended that you increase the NUMCPUVPS.  However, NUMCPUVPS is already set to the maximum for your system.  Therefore to improve performance, it is recommended that you buy more hardware.]]></NUMCPUVPS_RECOMMEND_ATMAX>
<PHYSBUFF_RECOMMEND_OK><![CDATA[Based on your database server's physical log writes, the current value of PHYSBUFF meets the recommendation of the OpenAdmin Tool.]]></PHYSBUFF_RECOMMEND_OK>
<PHYSBUFF_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[Based on your database server's physical log writes, the current value of PHYSBUFF is low.  Try increasing PHYSBUFF by 10 percent.]]></PHYSBUFF_RECOMMEND_NO>
<RESIDENT_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended to not have RESIDENT turned off.  If your server has RESIDENT set to 0, consider changing it to 2 or -1.]]></RESIDENT_RECOMMEND>
<RTO_SERVER_RESTART_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that RTO_SERVER_RESTART not be disabled (i.e. not set to 0).]]></RTO_SERVER_RESTART_RECOMMEND>
<QSTATS_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[QSTATS has a large performance impact when turned on, therefore it is recommended that QSTATS be turned off on production systems unless Tech Support has advised you to turn it on for debugging a specific issue.]]></QSTATS_RECOMMEND>
<SHMADD_RECOMMEND_OK><![CDATA[Based on the number of virtual memory segments in your database server, the current value of SHMADD meets the recommendation of the OpenAdmin Tool.]]></SHMADD_RECOMMEND_OK>
<SHMADD_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[Based on the number of virtual memory segments in your database server, it is recommended you increase the value of SHMADD.]]></SHMADD_RECOMMEND_NO>
<SHMTOTAL_RECOMMEND_OK><![CDATA[Based on this server's shared memory usage, the current value of SHMTOTAL follows the recommendation of the OpenAdmin Tool.]]></SHMTOTAL_RECOMMEND_OK>
<SHMTOTAL_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[If your database server hits the SHMTOTAL limit, application failures may occur.  Based on this server's shared memory usage, it is recommended that you increase SHMTOTAL to be greater than or equal to ]]></SHMTOTAL_RECOMMEND_NO>
<SHMVIRTSIZE_RECOMMEND_OK><![CDATA[Based on the number of virtual memory segments in your database server, the current value of SHMVIRTSIZE meets the recommendation of the OpenAdmin Tool.]]></SHMVIRTSIZE_RECOMMEND_OK>
<SHMVIRTSIZE_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[Based on the number of virtual memory segments in your database server, it is recommended you increase SHMVIRTSIZE to a value greater than the current setting but less than ]]></SHMVIRTSIZE_RECOMMEND_NO>
<SBSPACETEMP_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[Sbspaces exist on this server.  Therefore SBSPACETEMP should not be null and and each space listed should be an existing temporary sbspace.]]></SBSPACETEMP_RECOMMEND>
<SINGLE_CPU_VP_RECOMMEND_ON><![CDATA[There is only one physical processor on the database server machine.  Therefore it is recommended that you turn SINGLE_CPU_VPS on.]]></SINGLE_CPU_VP_RECOMMEND_ON>
<SINGLE_CPU_VP_RECOMMEND_ON_CHECK><![CDATA[It is recommended that you read the manual to understand the limitations imposed by SINGLE_CPU_VP and consider turning it on.]]></SINGLE_CPU_VP_RECOMMEND_ON_CHECK>
<SYSALARMPROGRAM_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that SYSALARAMPROGRAM be set to "$INFORMIXDIR/etc/evidence.sh" (UNIX/Linux) or "$INFORMIXDIR/etc/evidence.bat" (Windows).]]></SYSALARMPROGRAM_RECOMMEND>
<SYSALARMPROGRAM_RECOMMEND_NO><![CDATA[However, it appears currently SYSALARMPROGRAM is not set to a valid location.]]></SYSALARMPROGRAM_RECOMMEND_NO>
<TAPEBLK_RECOMMEND_LOW><![CDATA[The current setting of TAPEBLK is low.  Take a look at your tape drive specifications, as most tape drives support larger block sizes than your current configuration.  Increasing TAPEBLK could improve the performance of backups and restores.]]></TAPEBLK_RECOMMEND_LOW>
<TAPEBLK_RECOMMEND_HIGH><![CDATA[The current setting of TAPEBLK is rather high.  Take a look at your tape drive specifications to make sure it can support such a large value.]]></TAPEBLK_RECOMMEND_HIGH>
<TBLTBLFIRST_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that TBLTBLFIRST be set at or above the average size of this server's tblspace tblspace partitions.  The current sizes of your system's tblspace tblspace partitions are as follows: <BR>]]></TBLTBLFIRST_RECOMMEND>
<TBLTBLNEXT_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[It is recommended that TBLTBLFIRST be set at or above 25% of the average size of this server's tblspace tblspace partitions.  The current sizes of your system's tblspace tblspace partitions are as follows: <BR>]]></TBLTBLNEXT_RECOMMEND>
<TEMPTAB_NOLOG_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[When running in an HDR or Mach11 environment, if applications support it, it is recommended that TEMPTAB_NOLOG be turned ON so that logical logging on temporary table operations is disabled.  Turning this ON can improve your performance in the replication environment.]]></TEMPTAB_NOLOG_RECOMMEND>
<TRACEFLAGS_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[TRACEFLAGS can have a performance impact when turned on, therefore it is recommended that TRACEFLAGS be turned off (set to zero) on production systems unless Tech Support has advised you to turn it on for debugging a specific issue.]]></TRACEFLAGS_RECOMMEND>
<TRACES_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[TRACES can have a performance impact when turned on, therefore it is recommended that TRACES be turned off (set to zero) on production systems unless Tech Support has advised you to turn it on for debugging a specific issue.]]></TRACES_RECOMMEND>
<WSTATS_RECOMMEND><![CDATA[WSTATS has a large performance impact when turned on, therefore it is recommended that WSTATS be turned off on production systems unless Tech Support has advised you to turn it on for debugging a specific issue.]]></WSTATS_RECOMMEND>
</lang>
