<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<lang module="lang_act">

<act_r_DBSPACETEMP><![CDATA[ The DBSPACETEMP configuration parameter is not set.  For best performance with temporary tables and sort files, use the DBSPACETEMP configuration parameter to specify two or more dbspaces on separate disks.]]></act_r_DBSPACETEMP>
<act_r_DUMPDIR><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_DUMPDIR>
<act_r_DYNAMIC_LOGS><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_DYNAMIC_LOGS>
<act_r_Logdbs><![CDATA[The logical log files are stored in the root dbspace (rootdbs). Move the logical-log files out of the root dbspace to a dbspace on a disk that is not shared by active tables or the physical log.]]></act_r_Logdbs>
<act_r_LTXHWM><![CDATA[Dynamic-log allocation (DYNAMIC_LOGS) is off and the long-transaction high water mark (LTXHWM) is greater than %lparam1%. Set the LTXHWM configuration parameter lower to prevent long transaction rollbacks from hanging the system.]]></act_r_LTXHWM>
<act_r_LRU_MIN><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_LRU_MIN>
<act_r_LTAPEDEV><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_LTAPEDEV>
<act_r_NOAGE><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_NOAGE>
<act_r_ONDBSPACEDOWN><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_ONDBSPACEDOWN>
<act_r_Physdbs><![CDATA[The physical log is stored in the root dbspace (rootdbs). Move the physical log out of the root dbspace to a dbspace on a disk that is not shared by active tables or the logical log files.]]></act_r_Physdbs>
<act_r_SINGLE_CPU_VP><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_SINGLE_CPU_VP>
<act_r_TAPEDEV><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_TAPEDEV>
<act_r_ATS_Files><![CDATA[The number of ATS files Enterprise Replication is generating is greater than %param3%. Review these files and take appropriate action.]]></act_r_ATS_Files>
<act_r_ER_DDRBlock><![CDATA[The percentage of log pages remaining before transaction blocking (DDRBLOCK) starts is less than %param3%%.  Take appropriate action to prevent log wrap, which might include using dynamic log allocation.]]></act_r_ER_DDRBlock>
<act_r_ER_Down_Node><![CDATA[Enterprise Replication has detected that a node is down.  Investigate why the node is down and take appropriate action.]]></act_r_ER_Down_Node>
<act_r_RIS_Files><![CDATA[The number of RIS files Enterprise Replication is generating is greater than %param3%. Review these files and take appropriate action.]]></act_r_RIS_Files>
<act_r_OS_Free_Memory><![CDATA[The free memory that is available to the operating system is less than %param3%% of the total memory available.  A shortage of operating-system memory might result in performance degradation.  Take appropriate action to increase the operating-system memory.]]></act_r_OS_Free_Memory>
<act_r_OS_Online_Procs><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_OS_Online_Procs>
<act_r_OS_Procs><![CDATA[NA]]></act_r_OS_Procs>
<act_r_OS_Open_File_Limit><![CDATA[The number of open file descriptors per process for the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of open files per process might cause unexpected behavior for the database server. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_r_OS_Open_File_Limit>
<act_r_OS_semid><![CDATA[The number of semaphore sets in the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of semaphore sets might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_r_OS_semid>
<act_r_OS_semnum><![CDATA[The total number of the semaphores in the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of semaphores might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_r_OS_semnum>
<act_r_OS_shmids><![CDATA[The number of shared-memory IDs for the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of shared-memory IDs might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_r_OS_shmids>
<act_r_OS_shmmax><![CDATA[The maximum size of a shared-memory segment for the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  If the maximum size of a shared-memory segment is set too low, unexpected behavior might result. Take appropriate action.]]></act_r_OS_shmmax>
<act_r_OS_shmnumsegs><![CDATA[The total number of shared-memory segments in the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of shared-memory segments might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_r_OS_shmnumsegs>
<act_r_CKPT_Caused_By_LLOG><![CDATA[Blocking occurred during checkpoint processing because of a shortage of logical log resources. To avoid this situation, add logical logs.]]></act_r_CKPT_Caused_By_LLOG>
<act_r_CKPT_Caused_By_PLOG><![CDATA[Blocking occurred during checkpoint processing because of a shortage of physical log resources.  To avoid this situation, increase the size of the physical log.]]></act_r_CKPT_Caused_By_PLOG>
<act_r_Critical_Section><![CDATA[Some checkpoints have a critical section time greater than %lparam1% seconds.  Investigate the time spent in critical sections during checkpoint processing because it can cause blocking.]]></act_r_Critical_Section>
<act_r_Diskflush><![CDATA[The number of disk flushes per second during the checkpoints is less than  %lparam1%.  Investigate whether an I/O problem is causing slow disk activity.]]></act_r_Diskflush>
<act_r_Longest_Waiter><![CDATA[Some checkpoints have a wait time that is longer than %lparam1% seconds.  Investigate the cause to improve checkpoint performance.]]></act_r_Longest_Waiter>
<act_r_Buffreads_Per_Table><![CDATA[The number of buffer reads for some tables is greater than  %lparam1%% of all buffer reads.  Investigate the cause to improve performance.]]></act_r_Buffreads_Per_Table>
<act_r_Buffwrites_Per_Table><![CDATA[The number of buffer writes for some tables is greater than  %lparam1%% of all buffer writes.  Investigate the cause to improve performance.]]></act_r_Buffwrites_Per_Table>
<act_r_Seq_Scans_Per_Table><![CDATA[The number of sequential scans for some tables is greater than  %lparam1%% of all sequential scans. Investigate the cause to improve performance.]]></act_r_Seq_Scans_Per_Table>
<act_r_Buffreads_Cache><![CDATA[The percentage of reads that are cached to buffers (%cached) is less than %param3%%. The current percentage cached is %param1%%. Increasing the number of buffers might improve the percentage cached.]]></act_r_Buffreads_Cache>
<act_r_Buffwrites_Cache><![CDATA[The percentage of writes that are cached to buffers (%cached) is less than %param3%%. The current percentage cached is %param1%%. Increasing the number of buffers might improve the percentage cached.]]></act_r_Buffwrites_Cache>
<act_r_Disksorts><![CDATA[The number of disk sorts is greater than  %param3%% of total sorts. The current number of disk sorts is %param1%%. Investigate options for adding additional shared memory for sorts.]]></act_r_Disksorts>
<act_r_isrollbacks><![CDATA[The number of rolled-back transactions is greater than  %param3%% of total transactions.  Investigate whether the excessive rollbacks are due to application design or insufficient logical log resources.]]></act_r_isrollbacks>
<act_r_Foreground_Writes><![CDATA[The number of foreground writes is greater than  %param3%% of total writes.  Increasing the number of buffers might reduce the percentage of writes that are foreground writes.]]></act_r_Foreground_Writes>
<act_r_LLOG_Pages_Per_IO><![CDATA[The ratio of logical log pages to I/O (pages/IO) is greater than %param3%%.  The current ratio of logical log pages to I/O is %param1%%.  Investigate the size of the logical-log buffer (LOGBUFF).]]></act_r_LLOG_Pages_Per_IO>
<act_r_Lock_Waits><![CDATA[The number of lock waits is greater than %param3%% of total lock requests. The current lock waits are %param1%% of total lock requests.  Investigate tables with page level locking and concurrency in your applications.]]></act_r_Lock_Waits>
<act_r_PLOG_Pages_Per_IO><![CDATA[The ratio of physical log pages to I/O (pages/IO) is greater than %param3%%. The current ratio of physical log pages to I/O is %param1%%. Investigate the size of the physical log buffer.]]></act_r_PLOG_Pages_Per_IO>
<act_r_Seq_Scans><![CDATA[The number of sequential scans is greater than %param3%% of total SQL statements. Investigate ways to improve the performance of sequential scans.]]></act_r_Seq_Scans>
<act_r_Offline_Chunks><![CDATA[The check found that %param1% chunks are offline.  Investigate why the chunks are offline, and take appropriate action.]]></act_r_Offline_Chunks>
<act_r_Chunk_IO_OPS><![CDATA[The number of I/O operations for some chunks is greater than %lparam1%% of all I/O operations.  Investigate spreading the I/O operations more evenly across the chunks to improve performance.]]></act_r_Chunk_IO_OPS>
<act_r_Chunk_IO_Reads><![CDATA[The number of read operations for some chunks is greater than %lparam1%% of all read operations.  Investigate spreading the read operations more evenly across the chunks to improve performance.]]></act_r_Chunk_IO_Reads>
<act_r_Chunk_IO_Writes><![CDATA[The number of write operations for some chunks is greater than %lparam1%% of all write operations.  Investigate spreading the write operations more evenly across the chunks to improve performance.]]></act_r_Chunk_IO_Writes>
<act_r_Dbspace_Free_Space><![CDATA[Some dbspaces have free space that is less than  %lparam1%% of the total space in the dbspace.  Consider adding chunks to these dbspaces.]]></act_r_Dbspace_Free_Space>
<act_r_Rowsize><![CDATA[For some tables, %lparam1%% of the page cannot be used because of the page size of the dbspaces and the row size of the table. Investigate actions to increase the free space per page; for example, moving the table to a dbspace with a different page size or redesigning the table.]]></act_r_Rowsize>





<act_y_DBSPACETEMP><![CDATA[ The DBSPACETEMP configuration parameter contains space characters. Remove the white space between dbspaces.]]></act_y_DBSPACETEMP>
<act_y_DUMPDIR><![CDATA[The DUMPDIR configuration parameter is set to the %lparam1% directory. This configuration parameter specifies the directory where diagnostic information is created. Change the DUMPDIR configuration parameter to a different directory.]]></act_y_DUMPDIR>
<act_y_DYNAMIC_LOGS><![CDATA[Dynamic log allocation (DYNAMIC_LOGS) is off.  Turn on dynamic log allocation to prevent long transaction rollbacks from hanging the system.]]></act_y_DYNAMIC_LOGS>
<act_y_Logdbs><![CDATA[The logical log files are stored in a dbspace that contains active tables. Move the logical log files to a dbspace on a disk that is not shared by active tables or the physical log.]]></act_y_Logdbs>
<act_y_LTXHWM><![CDATA[Dynamic-log allocation (DYNAMIC_LOGS) is off and the long-transaction high water mark (LTXHWM) is greater than %lparam1%. Set the LTXHWM configuration parameter lower to prevent long transaction rollbacks from hanging the system.]]></act_y_LTXHWM>
<act_y_LRU_MIN><![CDATA[The value of the least recently used minimum dirty field (lru_min_dirty), %param1%%, is less than or equal to %param3%%.  With the introduction of interval checkpoints, increasing the value of this field might improve utilization of the buffer pool and performance.]]></act_y_LRU_MIN>
<act_y_LTAPEDEV><![CDATA[The LTAPEDEV configuration parameter is set to the %lparam1% directory. This configuration parameter specifies where the logical-log files are archived.  Set the LTAPEDEV configuration parameter to a different directory.]]></act_y_LTAPEDEV>
<act_y_NOAGE><![CDATA[The noage option of the VPCLASS configuration parameter is not set. Priority aging can occur when the operating system lowers the priority of long-running processes. Set the noage option to disable priority aging.]]></act_y_NOAGE>
<act_y_ONDBSPACEDOWN><![CDATA[The ONDBSPACEDOWN configuration parameter is set to continue (0).  When the database server encounters a noncritical dbspace that is down, the database server marks the dbspace offline and continues. The dbspace must be restored. Set the ONDBSPACEDOWN configuration parameter to abort (1) or wait (2) so that appropriate action can be taken when a space is marked down and the dbspace might not need to be restored.]]></act_y_ONDBSPACEDOWN> 
<act_y_Physdbs><![CDATA[The physical log is stored in a dbspace that contains active tables. Move the physical-log to a dbspace on a disk that is not shared by active tables or the logical log files.]]></act_y_Physdbs>
<act_y_SINGLE_CPU_VP><![CDATA[The SINGLE_CPU_VP configuration parameter is set and the MULTIPROCESSOR configuration parameter is set to 1.  To avoid unnecessary locking, set the MULTIPROCESSOR configuration parameter to 0.]]></act_y_SINGLE_CPU_VP>
<act_y_TAPEDEV><![CDATA[The TAPEDEV configuration parameter is set to the %lparam1% directory. This configuration parameter specifies where the archives are stored. Set the TAPEDEV configuration parameter to a different directory.]]></act_y_TAPEDEV>
<act_y_ATS_Files><![CDATA[The number of ATS files Enterprise Replication is generating is greater than %param3%. Review these files and take appropriate action.]]></act_y_ATS_Files>
<act_y_ER_DDRBlock><![CDATA[The percentage of log pages remaining before transaction blocking (DDRBLOCK) starts is less than %param3%%.  Take appropriate action to prevent log wrap, which might include using dynamic log allocation.]]></act_y_ER_DDRBlock>
<act_y_ER_Down_Node><![CDATA[NA]]></act_y_ER_Down_Node>
<act_y_RIS_Files><![CDATA[The number of RIS files Enterprise Replication is generating is greater than %param3%. Review these files and take appropriate action.]]></act_y_RIS_Files>
<act_y_OS_Free_Memory><![CDATA[The free memory that is available to the operating system is less than %param3%% of the total memory available.  A shortage of operating-system memory might result in performance degradation.  Take appropriate action to increase the operating-system memory.]]></act_y_OS_Free_Memory>
<act_y_OS_Online_Procs><![CDATA[The number of online processors in the operating system (%param3%) is less than the total number of processors (%param1%) in the operating system.  Determine why some of the processors are not online and take appropriate action.]]></act_y_OS_Online_Procs> 
<act_y_OS_Procs><![CDATA[The number of CPU virtual processors is less than %param3%% of the CPUs in the operating system. Increasing the number of CPU virtual processors might improve performance. Take appropriate action to increase the number of CPU virtual processors.]]></act_y_OS_Procs>
<act_y_OS_Open_File_Limit><![CDATA[The number of open file descriptors per process for the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of open file descriptors per process might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_y_OS_Open_File_Limit>
<act_y_OS_semid><![CDATA[The number of semaphore sets in the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of semaphore sets might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_y_OS_semid>
<act_y_OS_semnum><![CDATA[The total number of the semaphores in the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of semaphores might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_y_OS_semnum>
<act_y_OS_shmids><![CDATA[The number of shared-memory IDs for the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of shared-memory IDs might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_y_OS_shmids>
<act_y_OS_shmmax><![CDATA[The maximum size of a shared-memory segment for the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  If the maximum size of a shared-memory segment is set too low, unexpected behavior might result. Take appropriate action.]]></act_y_OS_shmmax>
<act_y_OS_shmnumsegs><![CDATA[The total number of shared-memory segments in the operating system is less than %param3%.  The current value is %param1%.  An insufficient number of shared-memory segments might cause unexpected behavior. Take appropriate action to increase this value.]]></act_y_OS_shmnumsegs>
<act_y_CKPT_Caused_By_LLOG><![CDATA[Checkpoints were triggered by a shortage of logical log resources. Potentially, a shortage of logical log resources can cause blocking during checkpoint processing. To avoid this situation, add logical logs.]]></act_y_CKPT_Caused_By_LLOG>
<act_y_CKPT_Caused_By_PLOG><![CDATA[Checkpoints were triggered by a shortage of physical log resources. Potentially, a shortage of physical log resources can cause blocking during checkpoint processing. To avoid this situation, increase the size of the physical log.]]></act_y_CKPT_Caused_By_PLOG>
<act_y_Critical_Section><![CDATA[Some checkpoints have a critical section time greater than %lparam1% seconds.  Investigate the time spent in critical sections during checkpoint processing because it can cause blocking.]]></act_y_Critical_Section>
<act_y_Diskflush><![CDATA[The number of disk flushes per second during checkpoint processing is less than  %lparam1%.  Investigate whether an I/O problem is causing slow disk activity.]]></act_y_Diskflush>
<act_y_Longest_Waiter><![CDATA[Some checkpoints have a wait time that is longer than %lparam1% seconds.  Investigate the cause to improve checkpoint performance.]]></act_y_Longest_Waiter>
<act_y_Buffreads_Per_Table><![CDATA[The number of buffer reads for some tables is greater than  %lparam1%% of all buffer reads.  Investigate the cause to improve performance.]]></act_y_Buffreads_Per_Table>
<act_y_Buffwrites_Per_Table><![CDATA[The number of buffer writes for some tables is greater than  %lparam1%% of all buffer writes.  Investigate the cause to improve performance.]]></act_y_Buffwrites_Per_Table>
<act_y_Seq_Scans_Per_Table><![CDATA[The number of sequential scans for some tables is greater than  %lparam1%% of all sequential scans. Investigate the cause to improve performance.]]></act_y_Seq_Scans_Per_Table>
<act_y_Buffreads_Cache><![CDATA[The percentage of reads that are cached to buffers (%cached) is less than %param3% %. The current percentage cached is %param1% %. Increasing the number of buffers might improve the percentage cached.]]></act_y_Buffreads_Cache>
<act_y_Buffwrites_Cache><![CDATA[The percentage of writes that are cached to buffers (%cached) is less than %param3% %. The current percentage cached is %param1% %. Increasing the number of buffers might improve the percentage cached.]]></act_y_Buffwrites_Cache>
<act_y_Disksorts><![CDATA[The number of disk sorts is greater than  %param3%% of total sorts. The current number of disk sorts is %param1%%. Investigate options for adding additional shared memory for sorts.]]></act_y_Disksorts>
<act_y_isrollbacks><![CDATA[The number of rolled-back transactions is greater than  %param3%% of total transactions.  Investigate whether the excessive rollbacks are due to application design or insufficient logical log resources.]]></act_y_isrollbacks>
<act_y_Foreground_Writes><![CDATA[The number of foreground writes is greater than  %param3%% of total writes.  Increasing the number of buffers might reduce the percentage of writes that are foreground writes.]]></act_y_Foreground_Writes>
<act_y_LLOG_Pages_Per_IO><![CDATA[The ratio of logical log pages to I/O (pages/IO) is less than %param3% %.  The current ratio of logical log pages to I/O is %param1% %.  Investigate the size of the logical-log buffer (LOGBUFF) and review the transaction throughput of unbuffered databases.]]></act_y_LLOG_Pages_Per_IO>
<act_y_Lock_Waits><![CDATA[The number of lock waits is greater than %param3%% of total lock requests. The current lock waits are %param1%% of total lock requests.  Investigate tables with page level locking and concurrency in your applications.]]></act_y_Lock_Waits>
<act_y_PLOG_Pages_Per_IO><![CDATA[The ratio of physical log pages to I/O is less than %param3% %. The current ratio of physical log pages to I/O is %param1% %. Investigate the size of the physical log buffer.]]></act_y_PLOG_Pages_Per_IO>
<act_y_Seq_Scans><![CDATA[The number of sequential scans is greater than %param3%% of total SQL statements. Investigate ways to improve the performance of sequential scans.]]></act_y_Seq_Scans>
<act_y_Offline_Chunks><![CDATA[NA]]></act_y_Offline_Chunks>
<act_y_Chunk_IO_OPS><![CDATA[The number of I/O operations for some chunks is greater than %lparam1%% of all I/O operations.  Investigate spreading the I/O operations more evenly across the chunks to improve performance.]]></act_y_Chunk_IO_OPS>
<act_y_Chunk_IO_Reads><![CDATA[The number of read operations for some chunks is greater than %lparam1%% of all read operations.  Investigate spreading the read operations more evenly across the chunks to improve performance.]]></act_y_Chunk_IO_Reads>
<act_y_Chunk_IO_Writes><![CDATA[The number of write operations for some chunks is greater than %lparam1%% of all write operations.  Investigate spreading the write operations more evenly across the chunks to improve performance.]]></act_y_Chunk_IO_Writes>
<act_y_Dbspace_Free_Space><![CDATA[Some dbspaces have free space that is less than  %lparam1%% of total space in the dbspace.  Consider adding chunks to these dbspaces.]]></act_y_Dbspace_Free_Space>
<act_y_Rowsize><![CDATA[For some tables, %lparam1%% of the page cannot be used because of the page size of the dbspaces and the row size of the table. Investigate actions to increase the free space per page; for example, moving the table to a dbspace with a different page size or redesigning the table.]]></act_y_Rowsize>

</lang>
